<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->
<events>
  <event>
    <title>50th Anniversary Episode</title>
    <date>23-11-2013</date>
    <description>"The Day of the Doctor" is a special episode of the British science fiction television programme Doctor Who, marking the programme's 50th anniversary. It was written by Steven Moffat, an executive producer alongside Faith Penhale. It was shown on BBC One on 23 November 2013, in both 2D and 3D. The special was broadcast simultaneously in 94 countries, and was shown concurrently in 3D in some cinemas. It achieved the Guinness World Record for the largest ever simulcast of a TV drama and won the Radio Times Audience Award at the 2014 British Academy Television Awards</description>
    <people>
      <person>David Tennant</person>
      <person>Matt Smith</person>
      <person>John Hurt</person>
      <person>Steven Moffat</person>
    </people>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>13th Doctor Revealed</title>
    <date>14-Dec-2017</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>First Episode Airs</title>
    <date>14-Dec-1963</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>Peter Capaldi's Last Episode</title>
    <date>25-Jan-2018</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>Matt Smith's Last Episode</title>
    <date>25-Jan-2014</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>William Hartnell's Last Episode</title>
    <date>14-Dec-1966</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>BBC announces that Doctor Who will return after 9 years</title>
    <date>26-Oct-2003</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>"Rose" episode is broadcast</title>
    <date>26-Apr-2005</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>David Tennant announced as Tenth Doctor</title>
    <date>16-May-2005</date>
    <description>No Description Supplied</description>
  </event>
  <event>
    <title>The Five Doctors (20th Anniversary Episode) is broadcast</title>
    <date>23-Dec-1983</date>
    <description>The Five Doctors is a special feature-length episode of the British science fiction television series Doctor Who, produced in celebration of the programme's 20th anniversary. It had its world premiere in the United States, on the Chicago PBS station WTTW and various other PBS member stations on 23 November 1983, the anniversary date. It was transmitted in the United Kingdom two days later.

The episode aired after the conclusion of the 20th season to celebrate the 20th anniversary. Patrick Troughton and Jon Pertwee reprised their roles as the Second and Third Doctors respectively. Richard Hurndall portrayed the First Doctor, as the character's original actor, William Hartnell, had died since his last appearance on the show ten years previously. Since Tom Baker decided not to appear in this special, footage from the unfinished serial Shada was used to portray the Fourth Doctor.</description>
    <people>
      <person>Peter Davison</person>
      <person>Richard Hurndall</person>
      <person>Patrick Troughton</person>
      <person>Jon Pertwee</person>
      <person>Tom Baker</person>
    </people>
  </event>
</events>
